Guide to the Stanford University Poster Collection SC1030
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Posters
  - Campus Revolts, 1968; 905-44; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
    Films- Misc.
  - Can documentary film change the world? 8 thesis films by students in the MFA Program in Documentary Film and Video. Saturday, June 12th, 2010- Cubberley Auditorium, 2010-011; 11 x 17 inches (Box A5)
  - "Candaules, Commissioner", 1968; 5123; 11 x 17 inches (Box not specified)
    Stanford Repertory Theater
  - Cantinflas, Un-dated; 905-5; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
    Drama- Miscellaneous
  - Cap and Gown Measurement, 1968; 530-6; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Cap and Gown Measurement, 1969; 530-13; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Cap and Gown Stanford Calendar, Un-dated; 530-26; 12 x 14 inches (Box B3)
  - "Cardinal Virtue", 1941; 5033; 14 x 22 (Box C7)
    Dramatists' Alliance Productions
  - Carnival, 530-20; 5 1/2 x 8 inches (Box A4)
  - carp diem. ditch that fishbowl. Come serve with us in a ministry of praise, prayer, fellowship, and son. testimony a cappella [auditions] [undated, picked up in 2006-], 2006-039; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Celebracion del 5 de Mayo Stanford University, 1983; 530-34; 23 x 17.5 inches (Box C9)
  - Celebrando el Cinco de Mayo Stanford University 1999, 2002-013; 12 x 19 inches (Box B1)
  - Celebrate women's history. Stanford University. Feb. 25 to Mar. 6, 1987, 2141; 11 x 17 inches (Box not specified)
    in mylar
    Feminist Studies
  - Celebrate women's history. Stanford University. Febryary 25 to March 6, 1987., 21401; 11x17 inches (Box A2)
  - Centenary Sunday, 1915; 317; 11 x 14 inches (Box A6)
  - Centennial, The Poem; Celebrating Stanford's First 100 Years. Poem by Bob Simon, illustration by Mary Burkhardt, 2000; 2002-002; 32 x 18 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
    Stanford centennial
  - Center for African Studies: Africa Table Fall Lecture Series, undated; 2015-015; 11 x 17 inches (Box A6)
    Center for African Studies
  - Century of Revolutions Lenin to Gorbachev. An exhibit of papers and documents..., 1990; 2152; 14 x 20.5 inches (Box not specified)
    hoover institution
  - Chamber Music of the Classical Period, 1965; 2014; 29 x 20 inches (Box D2)
    Libraries -- Lectures/Exhibits
  - Charity Base Ball Benefit of Oakland Free Kindergarten University of California vs Leland Stanford Jr. University. Saturday April 18, 1893, 2011-001; 11 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
    Brittle--one edge is broken off but present. From Wreden, but unaccessioned
  - "Charley's Aunt", Un-dated; 513-42; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Chas. R. Brown, "The Highest Form of Reward.", Un-dated; 391; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Chicago Blues- Buddy Guy, Un-dated; 901-14; 10.5 x 16 inches (Box A4)
    Concerts
  - Cheech and Chong, 1972 Jun 23 (Box A1)
  - Chicana/o Colloquia 1994-1995, 212-1; 11 x 17 inches (Box not specified)
  - Chicana/o Colloquia 1994-1995, 212-01; 11x17 inches (Box A1)
    Chicana/o Fellows p\Program
  - Chicano Colloquia, Un-dated; 212-2; 11 x 17 inches (Box not specified)
  - Chicano Colloquia, Un-dated; 212-7; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Chicano Colloquia, Un-dated; 212-02; 11x17 inches (Box A1)
  - Chicano Colloquia, 1998; 212-08; 11x17 inches (Box not specified)
  - Chicano Colloquia, Un-dated; 212-07; 11x17 inches (Box not specified)
  - Chicano Colloquia. Stanford University 1988 Jan.--Apr., 212-8; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Chicano Literary Criticism in a Social Context. A National Conference sponsored by Stanford Humanities Center, 1987; 416; 17 x 22 inches (Box D2)
  - Chicanos in California / Organizations, Politics, and People / An Exhibition Selected from the Chicano Manuscript Collections / April 24-June 30, 1983. Department of Special Collections., 2008-006; 19 x 12.5 inches (Box not specified)
  - Chicanos in the Political Process. Lecture and Discussion Series. Casa Zapata Dining Room, Stern Hall, Stanford University. [1979 or 1984], 2006-043; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Children and Childishness Revisited, Emma Rothschild. The 14th Annual Bliss Carnochan Lecture, April 7, 2006-, 2006-005; 14.5 x 24.5 inches (Box C4)
  - Chocolate Heads Motion Hymnary. Choreography by Aleta Hayes, 2011; 2011-002; 11 x 17 inches (Box GW403)
  - Christensen Distinguished Lecture. Michael Fried, Anri Sala's "Long Sorrow," April 30, 2009. Annenberg Auditorium., 2009-01-0; 11 x 17 inches (Box B3)
  - Christian Science Organization, 1968; 5182; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - Christmas Organ Recital, 1959; 202-4; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
    Music, Dept. of -- Recitals
  - Christmas Service, Un-dated; 24; 8x11 inches (Box A1)
    Religious Services-General
  - Chrome on Grass, 1968; 905-57; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - Chronotypes The Construction of Time. Stanford University February 13-15, 1988 History Corner. [Includes list of speakers], 2006-058; 17.5 x 23.5 inches (Box C4)
    Transferred to Archives by Exhibit staff Nov. 2006- who indicated it's a Barbara Mendelsohn design, but there is no acknowledgement on poster itself.
  - Cinco De Mayo, 1993, 532-07; 15.5x22 inches (Box C3)
    El Centro Chicano
  - Class Activities--'14 Gets '13's Poster Again, 1912; 501-31; 9x15 inches (Box A2)
    5/2001 repaired and encapsulated by CONS
    Class Activities
  - Class Activities--'14-Through Artless Halm, Falls Into '13 Trap, 1912; 501-30; 6x9 inches (Box A4)
  - Class Activities--"A Corner Knocked Off", 1906; 501-12; 22x28 inches (Box D2)
  - Class Activities--"Ace High", 1926; 501-41; 14x22 (Box C2)
  - Class Activities--"Adam and Eva", 1922; 501-34; 14x22 (Box C2)
  - Class Activities--"Butterfly Isle", 1907; 501-16; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Class Activities--"Captain Applejack", 1926; 501-40; 14x22 (Box C2)
  - Class Activities--"Charlie Brown Goes Formal", 1966; 501-47; 1`4x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Class Activities--"Cousin Kate", 1910; 501-28; 16x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Class Activities--"David Garrick", 1904; 501-9; 13x21 inches (Box not specified)
  - Class Activities--"Doctor Jordan Will Wear Bloomers in the Quad", Un-dated; 501-67; 28x42 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Class Activities--"Dulcy", 1927; 501-42; 14x22 (Box C2)
  - Class Activities--"Expressing willie.", Un-dated; 501-62; 14x20 (Box B1)
  - Class Activities--"Iolanthe", 1910; 501-27; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Class Activities--"Jordan Will Be Given the Hook", 1910; 501-26; 28x44 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Class Activities--"La Serena", 1907; 501-21; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Class Activities--"Monster Aggreation" [Aggretation?], 1898; 501-2; 12x24 inches (Box C3)
    5/2001 cleaned and repaird by CONS
  - Class Activities--"No Chaperones at the Minstrel Show", 1902-; 501-5; 28x44 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Class Activities--"One of the Family.", Un-dated; 501-61; 14x20 inches (Box B1)
  - Class Activities--"Rufus and Rittenhouse Run riot", 1907; 501-18; 28x44 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Class Activities--"She Stoops to Conquer", 1906; 501-13; 14x22 inches (Box map case)
  - Class Activities--"She Stoops to Conquer", 1906; 501-13; 14x22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Class Activities--"So Far Is Eden": A South Sea, Rum Smugglers Musical Comedy, 1924; 501-37; 14x22 (Box C2)
    Calss Activities
  - Class Activities--"South Seas Preferred.", 1929; 501-43; 14x22 inches (Box B1)
  - Class Activities--"Stanford: The Life Strenuous" [play by Class of 1907], 1906; 501-14; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
    Same image as 501-75 but in better condition
  - Class Activities--"Stanford: The Life Strenuous." [play by Class of 1907], 1906; 501-75; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
    Pasted on board; not in good condition
  - Class Activities--"Stanford: The Life Strenuous" [play by Class of 1907], 1906; 501-15; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Class Activities--"The Black Demon of '26 Serves all Frosh Their Desserts", 1923; 501-68; 24x36 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Class Activities--"The Bone of contention", Un-dated; 501-63; 11x14 inches (Box A2)
  - Class Activities--"The Fall of a Star", 1905-; 501-11; 22x28 inches (Box not specified)
  - Class Activities--"The Fleecers", 1908; 501-22; 28x44 inches (Box not specified)
  - Class Activities--"The Haunted House", A Mystery Farce by Owen Davis., Un-dated; 501-65; 14x22 inches (Box B1)
  - Class Activities--"The Hottentot", 1923; 501-36; 11x14 inches (Box A2)
  - Class Activities--"The Liars", 1909; 501-23; 13x22 (Box C2)
  - Class Activities--"The Rivals", 1905-; 501-10; 14x28 inches (Box not specified)
    5/95-in 341 map case
  - Class Activities--"The Second Plug Ugly.", Un-dated; 501-57; 11x14 (Box A2)
  - Class Activities--"Three Live Ghosts", 1925; 501-38; 14x22 (Box C2)
  - Class Activities--"Up on a Ladder.", Un-dated; 501-60; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Class Activities--"Wedding Bells", 1921; 501-64; 11x14 inches (Box A6)
  - Class Activities--"You Can Never Tell.", 1921; 501-44; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Class Activities--"You Can Never Tell", 1907; 501-17; 14x22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Class Activities--"You Can Never Tell", 1907; 501-17; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Class Activities--By This Sign We Conquer, 1925; 501-39; 24x34 inches (Box C7)
  - Class Activities--By This Sign We Conquer, 1925; 501-39; 17.5x26 inches (Box not specified)
    Reproduction of Original
  - Class Activities--Campus Goes Wet, 1920; 501-33; 18x32 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Class Activities--Campus Goes Wet, 1920; 501-33; 18x32 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
    5/2001 repaired by CONS
  - Class Activities--Campus Goes Wet 1920 (reproduction of original), 501-33; 14.75x26 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
    9/95-in 341 map case [6/2007 need to verify that 33b is with 33 in folder]
  - Class Activities--Frosh Death Notice, 1922; 501-35; 22x29 inches (Box not specified)
  - Class Activities--Have Patience If You Can't Have Anything Else!, 1904; 501-8; 25x36 inches (Box not specified)
    not sure if more than one copy of this exists
  - Class Activities--Have Patience If You Can't Have Anything Else!, 1904; 501-8; 22 X 28.5 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
    Treated and encapsulated by Conservation 2001
  - Class Activities--In the Clutches of the Baron, 1903-; 501-6; 28x44 inches (Box not specified)
  - Class Activities--Junior Day Farce, Un-dated; 501-58; 44x28 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Class Activities--Junior Day Festivities, 1899; 501-3; 23x15 inches (Box C3)
  - Class Activities--Junior Day Festivities, 1988; 501-69; 16x22 1/2 inches (Box C3)
  - Class Activities--Junior Plug Ugly, n.1904; 501-7; 14x28 inches (Box not specified)
  - Class Activities--Pajama Dance, 1958; 501-46; 18x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Class Activities--Senior Ball, 1966; 501-48; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Class Activities--Senior Ball, 1969; 501-55; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Class Activities--Senior Circus, Un-dated; 505-9; 23x32 inches (Box map case)
  - Class Activities--Senior Circus, Un-dated; 501-59; 23x32 inches (Box C3)
  - Class Activities--Senior Circus, Un-dated; 501-56; 42x28 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Class Activities--Senior Class Law Forum, Un-dated; 501-66; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Class Activities--Senior Class Officers, 1969; 501-54; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Class Activities--Senior Faculty cocktail Party, 1969; 501-52; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Class Activities--Senior Faculty Reception, 1967; 501-49; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Class Activities--Senior Happy Hour, 1969; 501-51; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Class Activities--Senior Happy Hour, 1968; 501-50; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Class Activities--Senior Oficers, 1969; 501-53; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Class Activities--Sixteen Statutes for Filthy Frosh, 1916; 501-32; 28x44 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Class Activities--Smeared, 1911; 501-29; 32x14 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Class Activities--Sophomores Go Ape, 1955; 501-45; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Class Activities--The Rule of Twelve, 1909; 501-25; 17x23 inches (Box not specified)
  - Class Activities--Who is Tixe?, 1907; 501-19; 9x12 inches (Box A2)
  - Class Avtivities--"Greatest Show on Earth", 1892; 501-1; 15x20 (Box C2)
  - Clear the Track, 1902-; 530-1; 13 x 20 inches (Box not specified)
  - Clifton de Berry, 1964; 323; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - "Cock-A-Doodle Dandy", 1968; 5124; 11 x 17 inches (Box C7)
  - Cold War, The: Whose Creation?, 1969; 118; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - College Man and the Home, undated; 121; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - College Stunts Stanford and California Stars to appear in Vaudeville on the night of the freshman game October 27 [1899] at Golden Gate Hall. Stanford Glee and Mandolin clubs. California Glee and Mandolin Clubs. Every dollar goes to ..SU Constitutional Amendment Club., 524-38; 22 x 14 inches (Box C5)
  - Colors de Una Cultura, Un-dated; 532-03; 11x17 inches (Box A2)
  - Colors in the Universe, 1968; 350; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Columbia Revolt, 1968; 905-61; 11 x 15 in (Box not specified)
  - Combined Concert, Un-dated; 524-49; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Combined Concert Stanford and California Musical Clubs in one program. Specialties, Schwartz and Eichelbroth of California, Olshausen and Barkan of Stanford. Assembly Hall, Saturday Apr. 13 [probably 1901-], 524-43; 20 x 28 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Combined Glee Concert / Berkeley Glee Club Stanford Glee Club / Assembly Hall, Saturday, April 16th [ca. 1910], 524-51; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - Combined Glee Concert / Berkeley Glee Club Stanford Glee Club / Assembly Hall, Saturday, April 16th [ca. 1910], 524-45; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
    same as 524-51 but different color paper
  - come make art! Steven Siegel 23-30 april 2006-. Artist Steven Siegel will be on campus to create an artwork out of digital castaways..., 2006-008; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Coming--Stanford University Cobined Glee and Mandolin Clubs--40 members--Watsonville, Dec. 9, Opera House [no year noted], Un-dated; 524-53; 22 x 14 inches (Box C5)
  - Commute Club members have more...fun fitness me time money relaxation join us!, undated; 2015-022; 11.5 x 19 inches (Box B4)
    Stanford University. Parking and Transportation Services.
  - Complimentary Copy: Stanford Centennial 1891-1991 The Peninsula Times Tribune, 902-03; 11x17 inches (Box A2)
    Art Exhibits on Campus
  - Complimentary Copy. Stanford Centennial 1891 1991. The Peninsula Times Tribune., 9073; 17 x 11 inches (Box map case)
    display card from newspaper rack
  - Complimentary Copy. Stanford Centennial 1891 1991. The Penisula Times Tribune., Un-dated; 90703; 17x11 inches (Box map case)
    (in 341 map case)
  - Con Home Week, 1969; 530-9; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Concert--Stanford Girls' Glee and Mandolin Clubs--Masonic Hall, Los Gatos, Friday Evening, April 18 [1902-?], 524-47; 20.5 x 28 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
    fragile, slightly torn in places
  - Concert by the Glee and Mandolin Clubs Hotel Vendome Music Room February 16, 1900, 524-08; 14 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Concert by the Stanford Girls' Gee and Mandolin Clubs under the Auspices of Cupertino Branch of the Needlework Guild of America, H.V.A. Hall, Cupertino, November 9th [ca. 1910], 524-52; 14 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Concert of Choral and Organ Music, 1962; 202-5; 11 x 14 inches (Box A1)
    Music, Dept. of -- Concerts
  - Conference on the Russian Impact on Asia, 1967; 128; 20 x 26 inches (Box D2)
    Faculty/Staff -- Conferences
  - Conference on the Russian Intelligentsia, 1968; 117; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - Conference on Undergraduate Instruction, 1966; 116; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - Conflict and Social Change, 1965; 326; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A2)
  - Confrontation Politics, 1968; 352; 81/2x11 inches (Box map case)
    Non-Stanford Speakers-Panel Discussions
  - Congressman George Brown, 1969; 374; 14 x 22 inches (Box C2)
  - "Connecticut Yankee", 1950; 511-25; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - Contemporary Paintings from Alumni Collections, Un-dated; 701; not listed (Box A4)
  - Contours of Russian Language and Literature, 1959; 319; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - Course in Stage Classics Production, 1935; 905-78; 20 x 28 inches (Box not specified)
  - Courses on Women Spring 1979. Prepared by the Center for Research on Women., 2003-019; 17 x 22 inches (Box C4)
    Center for Research on Women
  - "Cousin Kate", 1910; 513-67; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - "Craig's Wife", Un-dated; 513-41; 14 x 18 inches (Box C7)
  - Criminal Minds by Robin Swicord, Directed by Leigh Sealy, July 15-18. Stanford Summer Theater, 1970s; 2003-008; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - Crisis in Rhodesia, 1965; 114; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - Crome on Grass / April 26 [dance poster; art by J. Paget-Fredericks], 1968 1980; 905-57; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A3)
    1968 is penciled on poster; there's possibly a date of 1980 following the artist's name
  - CROW Noon Lecture Series, Winter 1979. Gender and the Writer. Ellen Moers, Tillie Olsen, Al Young, Barbara Christian, Janet Lewis, Joyce Carol Thomas, Susan Griffin, Arturo Islas., 2003-005; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - CS+English, 2015-014; 11 x 17 inches (Box A6)
  - Cultural Arts Division TMU Presents Criticism & the Arts Series. The Critic & Popular Entertainment. Panel Discussion John Wasserman, Rolfe Peterson, Philip Elwood, Thurs. Oct. 31 [1969], 528-03; 14 x 22 inches (Box C4)
  - "Daisies on the Cartracks", Un-dated; 513-39; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Dances-Salsa Spectacular. Tressider Oak Lounge, Friday November 11 n.y (could be 1988 or 1994); 5199 (Box map case)
  - Daniel Trembly MacDougal, 1897; 302; 11 x 13 inches (Box A2)
  - Days of Concern. Friday April 12 Noon Rally White Plaza. Come to Dinner Faculty-Student Dinner Discussions in University Residences. [April 12-13, 1968], 526-05; 14 x 22 inches (Box C4)
    Student Political and Social Involvement
  - "Dear Brutus", Un-dated; 903-4; 14 x 22 inches (Box C10)
  - "Dear Brutus" by James M. Barrie, 1948; 511-13; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - Debate between SDS and Concerned Students, 1969; 521-7; 14 x 22 inches (Box C8)
    Debate
  - Debate on Vietnam, 1967; 521-5; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Debate on Vietnam / Stanford vs UCLA Wed. April 19 [1967]. Sponsored by Speech Dept. and ASSU Speech Association., 521-5; 14 x 22 inches (Box C4)
  - Democracy and Diversity, 1987; 90801; 11 x 15.5 inches (Box B3)
    Ernesto Galarza Commemorative Lecture
  - Deparment of Music--The Kimber Award: The 1967 Compition in Instrumental Music, 202-28; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Department of Modern European Languages-- A Three Act Comedy: El Baile by Edgar Neville, Presented by Professor Schevill's Spanish Dramatic Class, 1967; 2061; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A1)
    Modern European Languages, Dept. of
  - Department of Music--Music--December 1965, 202-16; 11 x 16 inches (Box A1)
  - Department of Music--Music at Stanford December 66, 1967; 202-23; 11x 16 1/2 inches (Box A1)
  - Department of Music--Recital, 1959; 202-3; 11 x 14 inches (Box A1)
  - Department of Music--Requiem Mass, 1963; 202-6; 11 x 14 inches (Box A1)
  - Department of Music--Spring 1965 (April), 202-11; 11 x 16 inches (Box A1)
  - Department of Music--Subscription Series 1964-65, 202-8; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - Department of Music--Tuesday Noon Musical, 1959; 202-2; 11x14 inches (Box A1)
    Music, Dept. of -Recitals
  - Department of Philosophy, Un-dated; 29; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - Dept. of History. History Seminar, 1969; 905-66; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A4)
    Special and Miscellaneous
  - "Der Freischutz" in English, March 6-8, 1947; 511-7; 14 x 21 inches (Box C5)
  - "Desire Under the Elms", 1952; 511-34; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - "Devil's Disciple", May 29-31,1947; 511-8; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - Diane Lindsay & Sue Fink in Concert with Debbie Fier. Saturday May 4th Cubberley Auditorium Stanford University. Womyn's Entertainment Forum [1985], 2006-050; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - "Don Juan", Un-dated; 5058; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
    Department of Speech and Drama Productions
  - "Don Juan", 1966; 5052; 12 x 20 inches (Box C7)
  - Donna Turner Smith; The Hungarian Quartet, 1964; 202-7; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - Dr. A. W. Palmer, Un-dated; 389; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Dr. Albert Parker Fitch: "To Stanford Men and Women.", 1910; 315; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Dr. David P. Barrows, Un-dated; 405; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Dr. Edgard Robinson: Stanford History, 1968; 112; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - Dr. Hugh Black: "Books", Un-dated; 401; 14 x 22 inches (Box C2)
  - Dr. Jordan will lecture in the chapel: Benefit of '99 annual, 1897; 101; 9 x 12 inches (Box A1)
  - Dr. Peabody: "The Christian Life in the Modern World.", 1908; 313; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Dr. Peabody's Lectures: "The Christian Life and the Using of Money.", 1908; 314; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Dr. Robert Chase: "Plastic Surgery.", 1968; 346; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A2)
  - Dr. Samuel M. Zwemer Address, "The Moslem World.", Un-dated; 384; 11x17 inches (Box A2)
  - Dr. William Horace Day, Un-dated; 404; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Draft or Jail, The, 1968; 905-63; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - "Dragon Inn", 1969; 905-70; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - Dramatic Council Production--"Broadway": A Drama of Main Street, New York, by Philip Dunning and George Abbott., Un-dated; 506-21; 12x16 inches (Box A2)
    Dramatic Council Production
  - Dramatic Council Production--"Proletariat Plus.", Un-dated; 506-37; 13x20 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--"Roadside", Un-dated; 506-38; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Dramatic Council Production--"South Seas Preferred.", Un-dated; 506-43; 14x20 inches (Box map case)
  - Dramatic Council Production--"The Chief Thing.", 1928; 506-7; 14x11 inches (Box A2)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Aren't We All?, 1926; 506-5; 14x20 inches (Box C3)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Berkeley Square, Un-dated; 506-20; 14x18 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Cock Robin, Un-dated; 506-27; 14x20 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Dandy Dick, Un-dated; 506-22; 14x22 inches (Box map case)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Death Takes a Holiday, Un-dated; 506-23; 14x16 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Granite, Un-dated; 506-12; 14x20 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Hamlet, 1926; 506-4; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Hay Fever, 1926; 506-6; 14x20 inches (Box C3)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Mardi Gras, Un-dated; 506-10; 14x20 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Meet the Wife, 1926; 506-3; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Moving On, Un-dated; 506-9; 14x20 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Mrs. Bumpsteat-Leigh, A Farcical Comedy, Un-dated; 506-24; 14x20 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Not Herbert, Un-dated; 506-8; 14x20 inches (Box C3)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Parade by Elaine Ryan Wallace, Un-dated; 506-29; 12 1/2x16 inches (Box A2)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Princess Ida, Un-dated; 506-34; 14x20 (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Romeo and Juliet, Un-dated; 506-18; 14x19 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--So This is London, Un-dated; 506-33; 14x20 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--The Adding Machine., Un-dated; 506-31; 14x20 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--The Hairy Ape, Un-dated; 506-13; 14x18 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--The Inspector General, 1931; 506-11; 14X16 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--The Ivory Door, Un-dated; 506-17; 14x20 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--The Mistress of Briony, Un-dated; 506-26; 14x 21 1/2 inches (Box C3)
  - Dramatic Council Production--The Mistress of the Inn, Un-dated; 506-25; 14x20 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--The Passion of Joan Arc, Un-dated; 506-16; 14x20 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--The Royal Family, Un-dated; 506-19; 14x18 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--The Second Man, Un-dated; 506-32; 14x20 inches (Box B1)